smoont.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Smoont

Smoont has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.  The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website.

Third Party Advertising

We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Personal Information

We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.  Since we do not collect any personal information on this Website, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

External Links

This site contains links to other sites.  Smoont is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.  To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Smoont website.  On some pages, you can make requests and register to receive materials.  The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name and Email address .

The Way We Use Information:

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers.  For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Our Commitment To Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us.
